Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - GEI: Student programs (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - GEI: General Feelers (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - GEI: Volunteer Pool & Resources (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - GEI: Interns (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - GEI: Sacramento Volunteer Center (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - GEI: Contacts: Former Students (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - GEI: Donor Software (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - GEI: Kudos (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - GEI: Logo ideas (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - GEI: Press releases (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - GEI: Donations list (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - GEI: Solano Press books (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - GEI: Elk Grove – Rutter Middle School (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - GEI: Solicitation Packet (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - GEI: Acknowledgements (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - GEI: Board of Directors meeting 10/1996 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - GEI: Board of Directors meeting 7/1996 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - GEI: Board of Directors meeting 3/1996 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - GEI: Board of Directors meeting 5/1995 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - GEI: Retreat facilities (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - GEI: In-house Training (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - GEI: space use 10320 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - GEI: Mailing list (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - GEI: Newsletter 3/1996 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - GEI: Mather RAB/BLT (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - GEI: Sacramento non-profits (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - GEI: Sacramento environmental non-profits (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - GEI: Friends of Mather (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - GEI: OEOC (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - GEI: ROP (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - GEI: Mather Community Center (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - GEI: BECOME (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - GEI: Cordova COM (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - GEI: Construction Project 10320 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - GEI: County bylaws and articles (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - GEI: Roberts (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - GEI: Trustees meetings and notes (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - GEI: GEF software (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - GEI: Directors/Trustees (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - GEI: Board of Directors meeting 3/1996 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - GEI: Board of Directors meeting 7/1996 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - GEI III: 91024.2 ETP Final Report (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - GEI III: 91024.2 ETP Course Handout Slovakia (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - GEI III: 92001 ECI Poland (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - GEI III: 92025 Hungary EIA/NGOs (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - GEI III: 92029 CCC Program & Products (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - GEI III: Slovakia CCC Materials (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - GEI III: 93071 Slovakia EIA/CC Carrying Capacity (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - GEI III: 04692.11.001 correspondence in (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - GEI III: Miscellaneous reports, newsletters re: grants (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - GEI III: Grant correspondence, memoranda (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - GEI III: Slovakia report & miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - GEI III: Slovakia #1 general (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - GEI III: Rachel Dagovitz (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - GEI III: Rancho El Chorro (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - GEI III: CIEL (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - GEI III: Rincon/Sonoran Institutes (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - GEI III: EPC- Moscow Grishin (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - GEI III: IDEX International Development Exchange (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - GEI III: Institute of International Education (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - GEI III: Miscellaneous correspondence, publications 1994-1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - GEI III: GEF timesheet MacKenzie (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - GEI III: GEF timesheet Roberts (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - GEI III: GEF timesheet Wessel (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - GEI III: GEF timesheet others (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - GEI III: Institute for Conservation Leadership (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - GEI III: Foundation receipts (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - GEI III: Funders (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - NAEP: conference 1994 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - NAEP: conference 1994: International EA: the Big Bucks? (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - NAEP: conference 1994: National Committee Meeting (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - NAEP: conference 1994: general (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - NAEP: conference 1994: Committee Chairs Meeting (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - NAEP: 1996 conference ideas (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - NAEP: conference 1995 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - NAEP: newsletter (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - NAEP: Environmental Professional 1994 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - NAEP: Board of Directors (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - NAEP: Board of Directors special reports 1994 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - NAEP: Board of Directors meeting 1/1994 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - NAEP: EDRI Environmental Data Research Institute (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - NAEP: Environmental Training Programs (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - NAEP: IECI (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - NAEP: International Committee report & notes 1/1994 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - NAEP: Futures workshop & Followup 11/1994 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - NAEP: AEP discussions 1996 conference (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - NAEP: Zonta International (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - NAEP: IAIA materials (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - NAEP: similar organizations (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - NAEP: International Committee outreach (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - NAEP: Letterhead (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - NAEP: miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - NAEP: General (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - NAEP: Conference 1993 course (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - NAEP: Conference 1993 Hungary paper (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - NAEP: Conference 1993 Myvatn presentation (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - NAEP: Conference 1993 Panel session IA (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - NAEP: Conference 1993 Russian Delegation (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Placer County: CEQA Audit Working notes, readings (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Placer County: Oak Creek EIR draft 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Placer County: Technical Appendices (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Placer County: Division of Environmental Health program guide 1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Placer County: Atlas (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Placer County: Environmental Review Manual 1992 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Placer County: Bohemia Wallmart EIR 1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Placer County: Auburn/Bowman Community Plan 1994 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Placer County: Auburn/Bowman background report 1994 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Placer County: Auburn/Bowman Community Plan EIR 1994 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Placer County: Auburn/Bowman addendum: Hidden Glen (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Placer County: Sun Valley Oaks EIR Addendum 1994 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Placer County: Development Services Department Report 1994 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Placer County: Permit & Resource Management Department 1994 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - GEI proposals 1992: City of Auburn Environmental Management (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - GEI proposals 1992: Chico Environment course (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - GEI proposals 1992: NBD: CIWMB/Apogee (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 04F828-EP Caltrans (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - GEI proposals 1992: NBD: Indonesia (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - GEI proposals 1992: NBD: Pipeline monitoring (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - GEI proposals 1992: Sweden-Hungary trip (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - GEI proposals 1992: ECI Poland 92001 see 00192 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - GEI proposals 1992: COE 92011 see 001192 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92013 Kirby Canyon Landfill (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92016 Humboldt County Landfill (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92017 Idaho (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92018 CIWMB permitting (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92020 GAI Europe (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92021 AC2 Midwest (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92024 NPS (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - GEI proposals 1992: 92025 Hungary EIA/NGOs (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - 7026 Sonoma County Landfill Site 33: Raptor Management Plan 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - 7026.101 Raptor Study (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - 7026 Sonoma Waste Systems Raptor Management Plan (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - 7026.101 Supplemental notes (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - 7026.102 Arborists (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - 7026.103 Butterfly study (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - 7026.104 Grazing Park (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - 7026.200 Landfill Study Area Meteorological Studies 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - 7026.200 Meteorological Studies (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 7026.300 Project Management (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - 7026.301 Management of Environmental Tasks (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 7026.304 Client Meeting Attendance (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 7026.303 Project Coordination (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 7026.304 Siting Study reports & comments 1991 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - 92012 Sonoma County CEQA Audit (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - 01492 Boreal (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 01792 Idaho LRPD General File 1993- (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - 01792 General File to 6/1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - 01792 Contract (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - 01792 Reports (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - 01792 Palouse Path (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 01792 Olmstead Brothers Plan (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - 01792 Comprehensive Plan 1985 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - 01792 Reports (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - 01992 Grass Valley (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - 02293.00.110 Contract (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - 02392.A File Index (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - 02392.00.010 General (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - 02392.00.001 Incoming (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - 02392 EIP (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - 02392.00.003 Teleconferences (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - 02392.00.011 Meeting notes (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - 02392.00.010 Contract (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - 02392.00.120 ESA contract/scope (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - 02392.00.404 Tree Survey (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - 02392.00.130 WESCO proposal (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - 02392.00.200 Initial Study (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - 02392.00.400 Weber Creek Fisheries Resources Evaluation (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - 02392.00.401 Cultural Resources Inventory 1993 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - 02392.20.000 EDID (El Dorado Irrigation District)/WRP CEQA coordination general 1994 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 02392.20.110 EDID/WRP CEQA coordination contract (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 02392.20.402 California Spotted Owl (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 02792 EDID Treatment Plant 1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 02792 EDID Treatment Plant (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 02792 Plant reports (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 03692 Bernau/Hannaford 1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 04492 Placer County CEQA audit contract (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 04492 Placer County CEQA audit (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 04492 Placer County CEQA audit (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 04492 Placer County CEQA audit (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 01592 Del Webb (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - 00690.00.100-210 City of Folsom General Administrative: File Index (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - 00690 Folsom: miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - 00690.00.100 Planning Committee agenda 1991 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - 00690.00.101 Water (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - 00690.00.102 Wetlands Management Policy (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - 00690.00.103Master Contract (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - 00690.00.104 St. John’s Legal (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - 00690.00.105 General Task Order (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - 00690.00.108 Distribution List (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - 00690.00.111 CEQA workshop (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - 00690.00.112 Environmental Assessment Process (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 00690.00.113 Stationery (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - 00690.00.115 CEQA process (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - 00690.00.116 Subdivision Ordinance Update (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - 00690.00.118 Subcontract Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - 00690.00.119 articles (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - 00690.00.120 Potential tasks (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - 00690.00.200 Consultant Recommendation Forms (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - 00690.00.201 Initial Study Forms (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - 00690.00.202 Environmental Consultant Evaluation forms (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - 00690.00.204 Weekly Status Forms (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - 00690.00.205 Proposal Evaluation Forms (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - 00690.00.206 EIR Review Forms (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - 00690.00.207 Task Order Billing forms (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - 00690.37-.55 Folsom File Index (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - 00690.10 Russell Ranch #2 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - 00690 92.11 Circulation element (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - 00690 92.12 Air Quality Modeling (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - 00690 92.13 Athletic Club (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - 00690 92.14: Housing Element Update (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - 00690 92.15 Dam Plan & EIS (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - 00690.43 92.16 Folsom: Folsom Business Center (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - 00690.43 92.16 Folsom: Folsom Business Center (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - 00690 92.17 Sacramento Savings (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 00690 92.18 Los Cerros/ Natomas Ditch EAFP (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 00690 92.19 American river Canyon (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 00690 92.20 Wilbur Creek Estates South (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 00690 92.23 Greenback Bike Lane (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 00690 92.24 Household Hazardous Waste Element (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 00690 92.25 Lexington Hills Park (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 00690 92.26 Oak Hills Church (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 00690 92.27 Intel (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 00690 92.28 Natomas Station Lot M (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - 7023 Marsh Canyon Project Development & Improvement Plan (MCP DIP): File Index (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 7023A final 1990 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 7023B Final 1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 7023B (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 7023C Final 1991 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 7023D Edits (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 7023.000 Summary (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 7023.01 Seismic Design (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - 7023.02 Sycamore Fault study (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - 7023.03 Static & Dynamic (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - 7023.04 Scope monitoring (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - 7023.05 Settlement Program (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - 7023.06 Post-Earthquake program (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - 7023.07 Landfill Design (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - 7023.08 Leachate collection (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - 7023.09 Groundwater monitoring (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - 7023.10 Grading Specifications (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - 7023.11 Leachate Tank Compatibility (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - 7023.12 Onsite Water Supply Well (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - 7023.13 Surface Water & Erosion Sediment (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - 7023.14 Marsh Creek Protection (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - 7023.15 HHW Program (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - 7023.16 Air-Flow Monitoring (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - 7023.17 Windy Day Contingency Plan (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - 7023.18 Gas Control Collection (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - 7023.19 Landfill gas management (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - 7023.20 Noise management (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - 7023.21-22 Landscaping Plan (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 7023.22 Ground Cover (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 7023.22.3 Revegetation (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 7023.22.4 Revegetation (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 7023.22.5 Tree & Shrub planting (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 7023.22.6 Visual landscaping (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 7023.27 TOE Berm (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 7023.28 Mitigation Berms (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 7023.29 Entrance Screenings (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Agricultural Land Reclamation Reports (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Biotic Resources miscellaneous publications. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Bureau of Reclamation (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Fish & Game 1977-1990 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - EIS example: Chevron EIS 1993 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - EIS examples: Chevron EIS material; Elk Grove Automall 1996; California Collider Commission 1988; Lake Tahoe Electrical 1978; Folsom General Plan 1988; Mobil Pipeline draft 1990; Broadstone Unit Staff Report pt.1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - EIS example: Broadstone Unit Staff Report pt.2 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous blueprints, photographs- Folsom, Marsh Canyon etc. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Forestry: periodicals, newsletters, brochures 1990-1996 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Forestry: periodicals, newsletters, brochures 1990-1996 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Forestry: Protection (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Forestry: miscellaneous Handbooks, reports (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Forestry: Erosion Control, Revegetation (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Forestry: Oak Habitat Restoration (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Forestry: Symposium Proceedings (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Forestry: newsletters, reports, brochures, etc. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - GEMS Accounting: CTC (California Tahoe Conservancy) etc. 1994-1998 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - GEMS Accounting: funding organizations for international projects (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - GEMS Accounting: GEMS/GEF initial business plan 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - GEMS Accounting: UTR invoices, etc. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - GEMS Accounting: UTR invoices, etc (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - UTR-CTC Chronological 1/1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - CTC/OPDM EIR process (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - CTC Phase II work items (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - CTC working file 7-8/1996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - CTC working file 6/1996 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - CTC working file 4-5/1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - CTC working file 3/1996 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - CTC working file 2/1996 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - CTC working file 6-8/1995 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - CTC working file 11-12/1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - CTC working file 9-10/1995 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - UTR 05393-1 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - UTR DC Trip (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - UTR 05393-2 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - UTR 05393-3 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Environmental Case Law- miscellaneous reports 1983-1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- R (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- S (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- S (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- T (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- U-V (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- W (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- C (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- C (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- C (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- A (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- K (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- L (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- M (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- N (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- O (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- P (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- P (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - 0593.01.400C FG correspondence in #2 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 0593.01.400C FG correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 0593.01.400A PIOP correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 0593.01.400 Lindstrom revised Phase I Report (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - 0593.01.400E LA correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 0593.01.400F ES correspondence in #3 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - 0593.01.400F ES correspondence in #2 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - 0593.01.400F ES correspondence in #1 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - 0593.01.400G Hargrove correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - 0593.01.400H Gibson & Skordal (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - 0593.01.500 GEMS correspondence out #2 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - 0593.01.500 GEMS correspondence out #1 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - 0593.01.600A CTC correspondence in #2 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - 0593.01.600A CTC correspondence in #1 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - 0593.01.600A CTC (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - 0593.01.600B OPMD correspondence in #2 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - 0593.01.600B OPMD correspondence in #1 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - 0593.01.800 comments draft (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - 05393.A OPDM contract 1994 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - 05393.A correspondence out (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - 05393.00 File Index (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - 05393.00.100 Team Cost Schedules (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - 05393.00.101 maps (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - 05393.00.102 permits (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - 05393.00.103 Schedules & Calendars (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - 05393.00.104 Software (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - 05393.00.105A Hydro Reports (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - 05393.00.105C Background (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - 05393.00.100 contacts (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - 05393.00.105B Erosion Control (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - 05393.00.106 Articles (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - 05393.00.200 Draft Scope (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - 05393.00.300 Meeting Notes (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - 05393.00.400A PIOP-MIG correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - 05393.00.400B QA/QC correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - 05393.00.400C FG correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - 05393.00.400D ERA/GIS correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - 05393.00.400E LA correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - 05393.00.400F ES correspondence in (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - 05393.00.500 GEMS correspondence out (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - 05393.00.600 OPDM/CTC correspondence in (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - 05393.01 File Index #1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 05393.01 File Index #2 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 05393.01.100A PIOP subcontract (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 05393.01.100C FG subcontract (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - 05393.01.100D ERA/Lindstrom (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - 05393.01.100D ERA/Fox (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - 05393.01.100D ERA/Etra (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - 05393.01.100D ERA/Hart (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - 05393.01.100F ES subcontract (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - 05393.01.100E LA subcontract (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - 05393.01.100G PM subcontract (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - 05393.01.100H G&S subcontract (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - 05393.01.201 SOW (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - 05393.01.201.1 SOW (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - 05393.01.201.2 working budget (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - 05393.01.201.2 working budget 1995 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - 05393.01.300 meeting notes (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Sustainable Development publications (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Sustainable Development publications (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Sustainable Communities publications (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Sustainability China publications (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Alaska 6/1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Alaska Sustainable Development conference 7/1997 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Alaska publications, photographs (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Alaska talk materials (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - American River File Index (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - American River Purchase Orders (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: NAEP (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 96001 Uganda (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 96001 APC (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 96005 Spain EIS (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: Lumos & Associates (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 95009 Jordan Marine Action Plan (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 95016 BETEL contract & finances (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 95019 El Dorado (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 95023 South fork American River (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01994 Elsmere Canyon (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 03094 Waterford (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 03194 FTB (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 03294 EDID rare plants (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01493.01 Taiwan Coastal (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 03293 American Canyon (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 03494 Natomas Ditch (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 03593 UTR (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04093 Argentina EA (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04393.1 Potrero Hills (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04393.4 Survey (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04393.5 Habitat (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04393.3 Regrading (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04393.2 CEQA (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04393.6 Bioacoustics (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04493 SMUD Cogan (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04993 Alyeska (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 05993 Carmichael (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01292 CEQA Audit (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01792 Idaho (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 02392 EDID WR (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 02393.2 EDID WR CEQA (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 02992 Carrying Capacity Seminar (Box 52, Folder 42)